advertizer.com 2006-10-14

# Greenlight Wireless :: Privacy Policy

**Updated February 14, 2006**

Protecting your privacy is important to Greenlight Wireless. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Greenlight Wireless Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. 

Greenlight Wireless collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service and to make a wider range of products and services available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products. 

We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, or participate in an online survey. In addition, when you register a new Greenlight Wireless service or ask to be included in an e-mail mailing list, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database. 

At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest. 

Greenlight Wireless safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

Greenlight Wireless uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all Web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases from us, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet. In order to protect your privacy and provide the highest possible security, Greenlight Wireless does NOT retain a record of credit card numbers used during sign up processes. Partial credit card information is maintained on a secure database, however, for use in the event of a reimbursement or refund. 

When you browse the Greenlight Wireless Web site, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse—not even your e-mail address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using. 

In some of our e-mail to you, we use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our Web server before arriving at the Web site that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. 

Greenlight Wireless does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. 

The Greenlight Wireless Web site contains links to other sites. Greenlight Wireless does not share your personal information with those Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via e-mail using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner. 

The Greenlight Wireless Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
